CASEY MOTHS



caseymoths@outlook.com

I am a full stack developer, a creative problem solver, critical thinker and passionate learner. I love new challenges and exploring new technologies and am constantly curious about design and user experience. I have a breadth of skills and look forward to bringing my passion for web development and my eagerness to learn to your organization.

EXPERIENCE



WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance, San Diego, CA March 2018 - Current

- Design and develop modern responsive websites for small businesses to increase exposure and sales
- Speak with business owners to identify their requirements, design sites, and outline schedules
- Develop concepts, control project flow, and ensure deliverable milestones are met

APPAREL LICENSING COORDINATOR

Mad Engine, San Diego, CA

March 2016 - Current

- Submit, track, and log all pre-production apparel samples and required reports in Licensor systems and through email as needed

SKILLS



COURSEWORK



HTML React
CSS & SASS Node
CSS Grid Babel

Bootstrap Gulp & Webpack

Javascript & jQuery API's

PHP Adobe Photoshop Wordpress Adobe Illustrator - The Complete Web Developer Course 2.0

- Javascript: Understanding the Weird Parts
- Modern Javascript from the Beginning
- Modern React with Redux
- React 16 with Redux
- MERN Stack Front to Back
- The Complete Wordpress Website Business Course
- Object Oriented PHP & MVC

EDUCATION



Professional Certificate in Translation & Interpretation (Spanish/English) University of California - San Diego 2007 - 2009

Bachelor of Arts - Spanish, Legal Studies University of Wisconsin - Madison 2004 - 2007

VIEW MY WORK

